[Music]
you
I'm Emily Chu global head of ESG
research and integration at Manulife
investment management manual life
Investment Management is a global asset
manager with about 400 billion AUM
globally invested across all major asset
classes I lead a team of global
investment analysts a team that's
growing and we are working alongside
portfolio managers and investment
analysts to better integrate ESG
information into the way we make our
investment decisions
we are also overseeing a global program
of engagement with companies on
sustainability issues in order to better
serve our clients through capital
preservation and risk adjusted returns
[Music]
we are an active fundamental bottom-up
research driven investment manager we're
very committed to that space and we
believe that ESG information because it
is more and more available because it is
more and more evidence that it's
affecting company performance but it's a
natural part of the research process for
all of our investment staff that means
that we are including history
information into our research processes
and we're engaging with companies to
better understand how they're positioned
for the macroeconomic transition towards
a more sustainable and low-carbon future
climate change is an issue of systemic
magnitude and importance and all
investors need to be concerned with how
it's going to affect portfolios from our
perspective we think a whole of house
approach makes the most sense and that
means that it needs to be tackled from a
number of angles in that regard we are
committed to the global investor agenda
on climate change which has four pillars
the first pillar is investments so in
that regard we are conducting scenario
analysis across our public equities and
corporate bond exposures and looking at
how different climate scenarios could
affect portfolio construction and
returns the second pillar is company
engagement we sit on the steering
committee of the climate action 100-plus
and are working with our peers on
leading and correlating and
collaborating on engagements with
companies that are part of the scope of
that initiative the third pillar is
disclosure we are committed to producing
T CFD aligned disclosure and have made
steps in that direction over the course
of 2019 and the fourth pillar is policy
engagement we have joined together with
over 500 of our Investor peers to
co-sign a letter to global governments
asking for more direction and
consistency of approach in the way in
which the climate issue is factored into
financial markets
we believe that sustainability as a
macroeconomic trend that's here to stay
and will be transformative but with that
said sustainable outcomes are not a
given and therefore it's important for
us as a severe large asset manager to
liaison some of our other leading peers
in this space in order to develop
practice share ideas and to collaborate
towards better ESG integration
throughout the capital markets
[Music]